pacermonitor.com 2017-02-10

# Privacy Policy

PacerMonitor, LLC ("We", "Us", or the "Company") respects the privacy rights of our users and knows that you care how information about you is used and shared. This notice describes the privacy policy for our website, PacerMonitor.com (the "Site") and is part of our Terms of Service. By using the Site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service.

  * We collect anonymous data from every visitor of the Site to monitor performance, improve our service, and to fix bugs. This data includes, but is not limited to, pages requested, Internet Protocol (IP) address, and browser and network information. 
  * We may use "session cookies" to keep track of your browsing session. If you click "remember me" when logging in, we may use "persistent cookies" to store your authentication information between sessions. Your web browser allows you to control and limit cookies on your computer. If you reject cookies, you may still use the Site, but your ability to use some areas or functions of the Site may be limited. 
  * You must register on this Site in order to use certain of the Site’s features and functions. During registration you will be required to provide contact information, consisting of your name, email address, password, firm name, and address. We also may require some demographic data or other personal information. 
  * We log many of the actions taken on the Site by registered users, including pages viewed, documents downloaded, and documents emailed to 3rd parties, to provide better service and for billing of usage. 
  * Certain customer plans and site features are provided for a fee. You will be required to submit valid credit card information to receive access to these features. Your credit card information will never be transmitted to or stored on our servers, but will be transmitted directly to, and stored by our billing gateway, which is a certified PCI Service Provider Level 1, the most stringent level of certification available. 
  * Some of the Site’s products, features and services allow a registered user to use their own credentials for the Federal Court’s PACER system to download information including documents and dockets. We may store your PACER credentials on our server to provide better service. Your PACER credentials will be securely sent (via SSL encryption) to one of the Federal Court PACER sites during the process. Please review their policies at www.pacer.gov for information regarding their use of this data. 
  * We employ industry standard techniques to protect against unauthorized access of data about you that we store, including but not limited to Secure Socket Layer (SSL) transmission of all pages. 

  * We do not share your personal information or usage activity with third parties. Some aggregated, and/or anonymized data is periodically transmitted to third parties, including Google Analytics, for traffic analysis and SEO optimization. 
  * The Site may use your email address to provide you with periodic email updates regarding docket updates, new case filings, and general news. You can choose not to receive these emails by opting-out on the Customer Profile page on the Site. 
  * We may use your registered name and email address to provide you with significant announcements about Site functions or services that you are registered to use, about this Site, about any user account you may create, about fulfillment of a specific transaction you have requested, or about other significant developments that may affect your use of the Site. 
  * If you have registered as part of a team or corporate account, certain usage information and submitted content including but not limited to tags and comments may be made available to other users on your team. Usage and billing information may also be provided to your employer. 

We may release information concerning your use of the Site (including, but not limited to, posted Public Content, registration information, and network records) when We believe in good faith that such release is appropriate to comply with the law (for example, pursuant to a statutory demand, subpoena, warrant or court order), to protect against fraudulent, abusive or unlawful use of the Site, to protect the Company’s rights or property, or enforce any contract between you and the Company. Business or Asset Transfer or Sale

We may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the transferred business assets. Moreover, if we, or substantially all of our assets, were acquired, or if we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of us or our assets may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we collect or use information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the Website or sending you an email. A user is bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses the Services after such changes have been first posted.

Please contact support@pacermonitor.com with any question regarding this Privacy Policy
